He's not in here.
He's not in here, either!
Where the heck...are you?!
We've finally...made it this far!
Where are you...?!
Where are you?
Sasuke!
Sakura, huh?
Sa...su...ke.
Sasuke...
So it's you, Naruto...?
You don't even have
parents or siblings...
What do you know about me?!
You've been alone from the start!
What do you know about me?! Huh?!
It's having the bond that
makes it painful!
You've no idea
what it's like to lose that...!
You're right.
I don't know about having
real parents or siblings...
If that's the case...
Why Naruto...?
Why do you go so far for me...?
To me, it's a bond...
I've finally been able to establish.
That's why I'll stop you!
If that's the case,
then why didn't you...?
Then I'll just break that bond!
Why didn't you kill me
back then?!
Is that how you wanted
to break the bond?!
Sasuke!
The reason's simple...
It's not that I couldn't break
the bond with you...
You're one who might be able
to use the same Mangekyo
Sharingan as mine...
However, there is one condition...
You must kill...
your closest friend.
It was just irritating to me.
Obtaining power according to
the method I heard about from him.
You're only alive because
of my passing whim.
When did he...?!
Come to think of it,
didn't you have a dream
of becoming the Hokage...?
If you had the time to
chase after me,
you should've spent that
time training or something...
Right... Naruto?
And that's why this time around...
You'll lose your life...
because of my passing whim.
There's no way a guy
who can't even save one friend...
can ever become the Hokage.
Isn't that right...Sasuke?
Sasuke...!
Naruto...
Show him...our...powers.
What's the matter...?
Why do you hesitate...?
You need my power, don't you?
Now then...
Who do you want to kill...?
You should know.
That you can't do anything
on your own.
SEAL
Break the seal completely!
I'll grant you all of my powers
if you do.
How...?!
I can see it now...
So this is your unknown power, huh...?
Who would've thought...
you'd have something like this
inside of you...
I see...
So you're an Uchiha...
My how you've grown...
To think you'd be able
to see me within Naruto...
That loathsome Sharingan...
So that's the power of
the cursed clan, huh?
It seems this isn't the first time
you've seen the Sharingan.
Then...you must be
the Nine-Tailed Fox, huh...?
That vision, and Chakra
more ominous than mine...
It's just like...
Madara Uchiha, from long ago...
Heck if I know...that person.
Homecoming
Did you find it?
All clear here.
Target acquired!
Uh-oh! It'll get into the village!
No way will we let it get away!
What the--?!
Where'd it go?
That way!
Hey, you squirts!
Hey!
W-We're sorry!
What're you doing?!
Sorry!
Sorry about that.
Ichiraku Ramen
I'm going out for a small delivery.
Whoa! Outta the way!
Sorry, pops!
Hey, Naruto!
No, I mean...
Konohamaru!
We've cornered the target.
Hurry up.
It'll get away!
No problem!
Why you--!
- Give it up already!
- Konohamaru!
I got him!
A ribbon on the right ear...
No doubt about it.
Ebisu Sensei, we captured
the lost pet target "Dora."
Heh-heh... Mission complete!
Oh, my adorable Dora!
I was worried to death about you.
Where were you?
I'd want to run away too,
if an old lady like that
were my owner...
Konohamaru!
All right, here is the reward.
Now then, let's go home, Dora.
How many hours did it take
you guys to catch a simple lost cat?!
But that cat was incredibly quick...
And he seemed accustomed
to running away...
I don't want to hear
any excuses!
A mission like this must be carried out
more quickly and properly!
You guys are not good enough!
I can't display my true strength
on a lame mission like this!
Say, Iruka Sensei.
Don't you have more of
an awesome mission for me?
Listen... Konohamaru...
Konohamaru, you guys just
became Genin.
There's no way I can give missions
like that to you right off the bat, right?!
It'll be D-rank missions
until further notice.
I can't be satisfied with that!
After all, in the future
I'm going to become
the Seventh Hokage.
Seventh? Not the Sixth?
Brother Naruto's going to be the Sixth.
Brother Naruto, huh...?
I wonder where he is right now...
I bet he'll return having become
an awesome Shinobi.
I have faith in him!
He's more of a Second Naruto
than a Seventh Hokage...
Naruto... Are you holding up okay?
No matter what, I'll get strong
and bring Sasuke back!
Quite a bit of time has passed
since he said that
and went off for real training
with Master Jiraiya...
Yes. Isn't it just about the time
he should be returning?
We need him to return.
After all, there will probably be
significant developments sometime soon.
Hey... Could that be...?
Yeah... No doubt about it.
Miss Sakura!
Oh, Konohamaru!
Where are you off to?
The main village gate.
I have to pick up the morning pedestrian
traffic ledger for Lady Tsunade.
You want to come?
It's been about two and a half years.
Yeah, it has...
And then that Dora cat suddenly
starts scratching me like crazy!
We had missions like that, too.
It kind of takes me back.
Come to think of it,
have you heard anything
from Brother Naruto?!
Nothing...yet.
I see...
He should be coming back soon, though...
Hello, Izumo, Kotetsu.
Oh, look who's here...
Why don't you head on into town?
You'll see something interesting.
Something interesting...?
Don't tell me!
He's having a ball...
This takes me back!
The village hasn't changed a bit!
Everyone! Naruto Uzumaki's back!
It's all so nostalgic...!
Yup! Yup!
They added GrandmaTsunade's
Mountainside Image!
For real...?
For real!
Naruto? Is that you, Naruto?
When did you get back, Naruto?!
Just now!
Long time no see, Sakura!
You've gotten taller than me,
haven't you?
Huh...?
Oh! You're right.
He kind of...got
a build since I saw him last...
So? You think I've become
a bit womanly?
You're fine!
You haven't changed a bit.
You just don't understand
the heart of a woman...
Brother Naruto!
Sexy Jutsu!
Ohh!
Wha--?!
How about that?!
Pretty nice waist, hips and bust, huh?!
Konohamaru...
I'm not a kid anymore.
And you too, shouldn't be using Jutsu...
like that...
That's right. It isn't just
your appearance that's matured...
I kind of feel a bit lonesome,
but you've turned out quite admirable,
haven't you, Naruto?
Knowing you, I bet you came back
having acquired some incredible Jutsu.
That's such a boring Jutsu!
Check out my freshly
developed New Pervy Ninjutsu!
Right... Like the New Pervy Ninjutsu...
Here we go!
Hey, you idiot!
You haven't changed at all,
have you, you jerk?!
After seeing each other for
the first time in like two years!
You make me do this
in barely two minutes!
What am I supposed to do
with the feelings of admiration
I had for you earlier, huh?!
- That short temper and incredible strength.
- I'm not the least bit lonesome!
- She's a second-generation Tsunade.
- Huh? God, I'm mad at myself!
Just like I thought,
Sakura hasn't changed at all...
In fact, I get the feeling she's
even more vicious than before...
Huh? Did you say something?
It's been a long time, you two.
I'm sure your training produced
good results, right?
Do you think we came back
without making progress?
It went perfectly!
Then show me those
results immediately.
Show you...?
You will take on a particular man.
I didn't send him on any missions
for the past several days
and had him standby
for this very purpose.
Your opponent will be...
Come in!
Oh!
Today at around five
in the afternoon,
Security Ninja were found collapsed
at the fortress of
the Village Hidden in the Sand.
No signs of dispute were found
within the scene of the crime;
leading officials to believe
the crime might have been committed
by someone in the village,
or a skilled intruder.
Around the same time,
there have been reported sightings
of two men dressed in black clothing
with red cloud patterns.
They are likely connected
to the incident.
Next time:
"The Akatsuki Makes Its Move"